Finding Aid for the William Campbell Binkley Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- WILLIAMS, Samuel C., (1937); 1
-----. Correspondence, 1951-1955. Seel Paul M. Angle, Harold W. Bradley, Fred Cole, Richard N. Current, Merle Curti, E. E. Dale, Dwight Dumond, Joe B. Frantz, Paul W. Gates, W. B. Hesseltine, George H. Knoles, Thomas LeDuc, Clifford L. Lord, R. C. McGrane, George Mowry, Clara S. Paine, Howard H. Peckham, Carl Coke Rister, James Lee Sellers, W. H. Stephenson, Harris G. Warren, Carl Wittke.
----. Correspondence, 1953-1954. See: W. Burlie Brown, Richard N. Current, Dwight Dumond, Donald E. Everett, Fletcher M. Green, R«gi-nald C. McGrane, George Mowry, James C. Olson, Clara S. Paine, Clarence S. Paine, William J. Peterson, James Lee Sellers, W. H. Stephenson, W. P. Webb, Carl Wittke.
-----. Secretary-Treasurer, 1953-1955. See: James C. Olson.
-----. Program Committee, 1954-1957. See Lewis Atherton, Gilbert C. Fite, Joe B. Frantz.
-----. Executive Committee, 1955-1956. See: George L. Anderson, James C. Olson.
-----. Publications Committee, 1955-1956. See: George L. Anderson, Dwight L. Dumond, O. H. Dickerson, James C. Olson.
-----. Seeretary-Treasurer, 1955-1956. See: James C. Olson, Paul R. Strain.
-----. Secretary-Treasurer, 1956-1957. See: W. D. Aeschbacher, James C. Oloon.
-----. Secretary-Treasurer, 1957-1958. See: W. D. Aeschbacher, W. 11. Stephenson.
-----. Secretary-Treasurer, 1958-1959. See: W. D. Aeschbacher, Wilbur R. Jacobs.
-----. Affairs, 1959-1960. See: W. D. Aeschbacher, Thomas D. Clark, Fletcher M. Green.
-----. Seeretary-Treasurer, 1959-1961. See: W. D. Aeschbacher, Irwin L. Grimes, Walter R. Nelson, Jerry Sallis, Robert W. Silsby, Phillip Thomson.
Mississippi Valley Historical Review, 1934-1946. See: Arthur C. Cole, Lester Driver, Bertha E. Josephson, Howard Kramer, Naylor Company, Louis Pelzer, M. M. Quaife, Torch Press.
-----. Budget correspondence, 1954-1962. See Roger P. McCutcheon.
-----. Staff - Recommendations and correspondence, 1956-1962. See: Jim Baughman, Lawrence Burnette, Jr., Joseph E. Dellen, Philip Detweiler, Emily Drum, Allen J. Going, Libby Greicus, Ralph W. Hidy, William R. Hogan, Marianne Komodore, R. A. Koy, Robert W. Lovett, R. M. Lumiansky, Beverly B. Madron, Mrs. John C. Sallis, Clarence Scheps, Robert J. Stone, Emily Swnaton, Sarah Van Woolfolk.
-----. Winter-Mooney correspondence, 1962-1962. See Chase Mooney, Oscar O. Winther.
-----. Correspondence, 1963-1964. See: W.D. Aeschbacher, Lawanda Cox, Sue Dye, Dorothy V. Jackson, James C. Olson, Bennett H. Wall, Richard L. Watson, Jr., Oscar O. Winther.
M.A. Candidates (former), 1933-1953. See: Elizabeth Claughton Bingham, William Blue, Dick Boiling, Addie Lou Brooks, Walter D. Cocking, Margaret Burr DesChamps, Morrill Donald, John O. Eidson, Luida B. Gallaway, P. M. Hamer, Isabelle Green Kegley, Margaret Kinard, C.S. Lowry, Charles D. Matthews, William E. Martin, Geraldine Meroney, Louise Osborne, F.C. Paschal, Elizabeth Peeler, J.E. Pomfret, Walter B. Posey, Lisle A. Rose, Leon F. Sensabaugh, Richard H. Shryock, Lois Thomas, Glenn E. Weekley, Evelyn Wiley.
NUCMC Paper, 1964. See Haskell Monroe, Harriet C. Owsley.
Santa Ana High School, Class of '10A. See: H.O. Eggen, Kate Hinton, Olive Kirkpatrick, Nellie Lolmaugh, Ed McFadden.
Social Science Research Council, 1933-1952. See: Carolyn E. Allen, Joseph B. Casagrande, Robert T. Crane, John E. Pomfret, Walter R. Sharp, Elbridge Sibley, Donald Young.
Southern Historical Association - Journal, 1934-1942. See John D. Barn-hart, Fred Cole, Thomas Kearney, W. H. Stephenson.
-----. Program, Birmingham meeting, 1935« See: Kathryn T. Abbey, Thomas P. Abernethy, E. Merton Coulter, Fletcher M. Green, L.G. Helderman, Charles M. Knapp, Ella Lonn, Ross H. McLean, H.C. Nixon, James W. Patton, C.H. Pegg, Walter B. Posey, Charles W. Ramsdell, Guy E. Snavely, W. H. Stephenson, M. Swearingen, Charles S. Sydnor.
-----. Nashville meeting, 1936-1938. See: J.M. Batten, Howard E. Baughman, Fred Cole, E. Merton Coulter, W.O. Daugherty, Frank Davis, Fletcher M. Green, W. Murray Hogan, w. King, Hill McAlister, Winifred H. McLean, James W. Moffitt, Edd Parks, Ralph Perry, Charles W. Ramsdell, Linda Rhoa, Culver H. Smith, Hill Turner, R.H. Woody.
-----. General Matters, 1936-1941. See: Sydney Banks, Thomas D. Clark, Edwin A. Davis, Fletcher M. Green, P.M. Hamer, Herbert A. Cellar, James W. Patton, Walter Prichard, T.H. Reynolds, W.H. Stephenson.
-----. Correspondence as President, 1949-1952. W.G. Bean, John K. Bettersworth, James C. Bonner, William A. Bultman, Lester J. Cappon, Jane Carson, Gordon T. Chappell, Paul H. Clyde, Elizabeth Cometti, E.M. Coulter, Avery Craven, Edwin A. Davis, J.H. Easterby, James S. Ferguson, Gilbert C. Fite, Milton Fleetwood, Tom Govan, U.S. Grant 3rd, Wood Gray, Kathryn Abbey Hanna, J. Wesley Hoffman, William D. Hoyt, Jr., Frontis W. Johnston, Lillian Kibler, A.D. Kirwan, Hugh T. Lefler, Thomas P. Martin, Joseph J. Mathews, Bernard Mayo, J.R. McCain, Shelby T. McCloy, Horace Montgomery, David Owen, Donnell M. Owings, Walter B. Posey, William H.E. Rachal, A.B. Sears, Henry T. Shanks, J. Carlisle Sitterson, C.W. Tebeau, E. Bruce Thompson, Lawrence S. Thompson, Nannie M. Tilley, Bla/ke R. Van Leer, Bennett H. Wall, Theresa Waller, Goodrich C. White, C. Vann Woodward.
-----. Presidential Address. See: Winnie Allen, Leslie E. Bliss, Harold W. Bradley, Frances Clifton, E. Merton Coulter, E.E. Dale, Llerena Friend, Fletcher M. Green, J.G. de Roulhac Hamilton, George Hammond, Lawrence F. Hill, W. Stull Holt, Robert W. Johannsen, Margaret Kinard, Joe Mathews, Clarence S. Paine, ^ames W. Patton, Charley Smith, Walter Prescott Webb, O.°. Winther.
-----. Secretary, 1942-1953. See: James W. Patton, J. Carlyle Sitterson, Bennett Wall.
-----. Correspondence, 1957-1963. See: Neva Armstrong, Werner H. Barth, Will D. Gilliam, Jr., William B. Hesseltine, John F. Merriam, R.W. Patrick, James W. Patton, Walter B. Posey, O.C. Skipper.
Southern Humanities Conference, 1946-1952. See: J.O. Bailey, Meredith P. Crawford, Hazel Farris, i<.B. House, John E. Ivey, Jr., Sturgis E. eavitt, Edward D. Myers.
Southern University Conference, Committee on Research, 1947-1950. See: Charles E. Diehl, Umphrey Lee, Edward McCrady, Logan Wilson.
Tennessee History, miscellaneous, 1931-1946. See: Kenneth Byerly, Paul G. Caywood, R.E. Clarkson, Arthur Crownover, Jr., Stanley J. Folmsbee, Olaf T. Hagen, S.E. Henderson, T. Marshall Jones, Samuel E. Linton, Fred W. Lorch, K.H. Mason, Stanley W. McClure, Abby Crawford Milton, C.D. Montgomery, W.B. Nicholson, J.M. Smith, P.M. Stevenson, Fremont P. Wirth.
Tennessee Historical quarterly - Judge Williams, 1941-1943. See Hallum W. Goodloe, Archibald Henderson, Stanley F. norn, RHW, Samuel C. Williams.
-----. Correspondence, 1942-1943. See: Mrs. A.M. Barrow, Addie Lou Brooks, H.M. Browning, Edmund O. Burnett, L. Dortch ^urton, John W. Craddock, C.C. Crittenden, Arthur Crownover, Jr., Sue Ellen Delaney, Mrs. John H. DeWitt, Emma Farrell, W.W. Faw, S.J. Folmsbee, Hallum W. Goodloe, Mildred Haun, A.H. Hepburn, Stanley F. Horn, Thelma James, Robert L. Kincaid, Guy Miles, James W. Moffitt, Mrs. John Trotwood Moore, Elizabeth Peeler, Louis Pelzer, James J. Snipes, Margaret H. Stone, Kate T. Stout, Charles S. Sydnor, David Y. Thomas, E. Bruce Thompson, Vanderbilt University Press, J.E. Windrow, Lillian C. Wuest.
Tennessee Historical Society. Correspondence, 1931-1951. See Clarence E. Carter, John H. DeWitt, Stanley Horn, Frank W. Prescott.
-----. Special Committee, 1937-1944. See: Clyde Ball, W.A. Bass, H. Hale Bellot, Cullom & Ghertner, Luther H. Evans, W.B. Haynie, W.B. nesseltine, Stanley F. Horn, R.B.C. Howell, S.F. Riepma, Samuel C. Williams.
Territory Papers, 1933-1952. See: Richard M, Atkinson, Harold H. Burton, Clarence E. Carter, R.S. Cotterill, Herbert Gambrell, George P. Hammond, Carl Hayden, Lister Hill, Cordell Hull, Elmer T. Hutchinson, J. Walter Lambeth, Archibald MacLeish, Thomas E. Martin, Burnet R. Maybank, Kenneth D. McKellar, J. Percy Priest, M.M. Quaife, Richard B. Russell, Mrs. Rutledge Smith, E. Wilder Spaulding, Walter P. Webb.
Texas State Historical Association, 1941, 1947 • See: Walter P. Webb.
Texas University Library, 1937-1941. See: Winnie Allen, David Coney, Keith Davis, Marcelle Lively Hamer, Charles Rothe.
Texas, University of, Press, 1967- See: David H. Gilbert.
Tulane University, 1963-1964. See: W.D. Aeschbacher, Herbert E. Longe-necker, William Peery, Clarence Scheps, John Snell.
Tulane, University College, 1968-1970. See: Emily Clarke, John P. Dyer, Robert C. Whittemore.
Texas Records Correspondence, 1962-1963. See: James M. Day, Joe B. Frantz, John W. Meaney, Frank H. wardlaw, Dorman Winfrey.
Texas, University of, Correspondence, 1930-1943. See: H.Y. Benedict, J.W. Calhoun, Mrs. P.S. Clarke, Milton R. Gutsch, Charles W. Hackett, Hilda Wilcox Phelps, Homer P. Rainey, Thad W. Riker, -Lorn Rousse, W.p. Webb.
Vanderbilt position, correspondence, 1930. See: Aileen Bishop, William E. Dodd, L.C. Glenn, Gerald D, Henderson, J.H. Kirkland, Charles C. Mierow, Frank L. Owsley, F.C. Paschal, Curtis H. Walker.